{
    "id": "ed1536fb8f924335a6672af3029bdaec",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I could answer only ………………………. questions.",
            "description": "Few means almost none a few indicates a small number. ",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t have …………………………. friends in the city.",
            "description": "Not any means the same as no.",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "any",
                "no"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. children like pet animals.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "The most",
                "A most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t got ………………………. money.",
            "description": "Use much with uncountable nouns and many with plural nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "more"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t find ………………………….. there.",
            "description": "Not anybody means the same as nobody. ",
            "answers": [
                "somebody",
                "nobody",
                "anybody"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There is ………………………….. to worry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nothing",
                "anything",
                "no thing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There are ……………………………. mangoes on the tree this year.",
            "description": "Use fewer with plural nouns and less with uncountable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He earns …………………………. money than I do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "few",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has …………………………… confidence in her skills.",
            "description": "Use little with uncountable nouns and few with plural nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few",
                "small"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You have never given me …………………………… help.",
            "description": "Use any with negative expressions like never, hardly etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "many",
                "some"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. of my friends are religious.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Much",
                "Most",
                "More"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. money has been wasted on that project.",
            "description": "Use much with uncountable nouns and many with plural nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "Much",
                "Most",
                "Many"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}